{
    "id": "acb0cca77c154aa696b676db9b16aba8",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Everybody was there …………………………… Samuel.",
            "description": "But can mean except after all, every, none, any or no.",
            "answers": [
                "except",
                "but",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. the storm, we would have been home before evening.",
            "description": "But for can mean if something had not existed or happened. Except for is not used with this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "But",
                "But for",
                "Except for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody but …………………………… would act so foolishly.",
            "description": "We normally use object pronouns after but subject pronouns are possible in a more formal style.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We got it out ………………………….. a screwdriver.",
            "description": "We use with when we talk about the tool or object we use to get a result.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It takes me only about 5 minutes to …………………………. ready.",
            "description": "We do not use become to talk about deliberate actions.",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "turn",
                "become"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t help …………………………. what they said.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after cannot help / could not help.",
            "answers": [
                "overhear",
                "overhearing",
                "to overhear"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t help but ………………………………. where she has disappeared.",
            "description": "After can’t help but we use an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "wonder",
                "to wonder",
                "wondering"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They got married in January, and got divorced six months …………………………",
            "description": "Later means at a time in the future or after the time you have mentioned.",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will make all your dreams ………………………………… true.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to after make.",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "came",
                "to come"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Everything came …………………………… in the end.",
            "description": "Come is used in some fixed expressions. Common examples are come true and come right.",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When did you ………………………….. to live in this town?",
            "description": "We use come to talk about movements to the place where the speaker or the hearer is.",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "go",
                "came",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to ……………………….. and live somewhere else.",
            "description": "We use go for movements to other places. ",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "go"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}